live-online-tv.com 2019-07-19

# Privacy policy

**TV channels** : [**News**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-news-tv-online-live.html "TV news TV online live") | [**Sport**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-sport-tv-sports-tv-online-live.html "TV sport TV sports TV online live") | [**Music**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-music-tv-online-live.html "TV music TV online live") | [**Cartoons**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-cartoon-tv-cartoons-tv-online-live.html "TV cartoon TV cartoons TV online live") | [**Movies**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-movie-tv-movies-tv-online-live.html "TV movie TV movies TV online live") | [**Games**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-games-tv-game-tv-online-live.html "TV games TV game TV online live") | [**Funny**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-funny-tv-online-live.html "TV funny TV online live") | [**Talk**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-talk-tv-online-live.html "TV talk TV online live") | [**Celebrities**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-celebrity-tv-celebrities-tv-online-live.html "TV celebrity TV celebrities TV online live") | [**Fashion**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-fashion-tv-online-live.html "TV fashion TV online live") | [**Education**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-education-tv-online-live.html "TV education TV online live") | [**Travel**](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-travel-tv-online-live.html "TV travel TV online live") | [**Poker**](http://www.online-poker-tv.com/ "TV Poker TV PokerTV Live Online") | [**Sex TV**](http://www.adult-sex-porn-tv.com/ "Adult TV Sex TV Porn TV Porno free live online")   
**Local TV channels** : [Australia](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Australia-tv-online-live.html "TV Australia TV online live") | [Austria](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Osterreich-tv-online-live.html "TV �sterreich TV online live") | [Belgium](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Belgie-tv-Belgique-tv-online-live.html "TV Belgi� TV Belgique TV online live") | [Canada](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Canada-tv-online-live.html "TV Canada TV online live") | [Denmark](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Danmark-tv-online-live.html "TV Danmark TV online live") | [Finland](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Suomi-tv-online-live.html "TV Suomi TV online live") | [France](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-France-tv-online-live.html "TV France TV online live") | [Germany](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Deutschland-tv-online-live.html "TV Deutschland TV online live") | [Greenland](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Gronland-tv-online-live.html "TV Grønland TV online live") | [Iceland](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Iceland-tv-online-live.html "TV �sland TV Iceland TV online live") | [Latvia](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Latvijas-tv-online-live.html "TV Latvijas TV online live") | [Lithuania](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Lietuvos-tv-online-live.html "TV Lietuvos TV online live") | [Luxembourg](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Letzebuerg-tv-Luxembourg-tv-online-live.html "TV L�tzebuerg TV Luxembourg TV online live") | [Moldova](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Moldova-tv-online-live.html "TV Moldova TV online live") | [Netherlands](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Nederland-tv-online-live.html "TV Nederland TV online live") | [New Zealand](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-New-Zealand-tv-online-live.html "TV New Zealand TV online live") | [Norway](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Norge-tv-online-live.html "TV Norge TV online live") | [Romania](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Romania-tv-online-live.html "TV Romania TV online live") | [Sweden](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Sverige-tv-online-live.html "TV Sverige TV online live") | [Switzerland](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-Schweiz-tv-Suisse-tv-online-live.html "TV Schweiz TV Suisse TV online live") | [United Kingdom](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-United-Kingdom-tv-online-live.html "TV United Kingdom TV online live") | [United States local](http://www.live-online-tv.com/tv-USA-tv-online-live.html "TV USA TV online live")

**Privacy Policy**   
We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy.   
**What information do we collect ?**   
We do not require that users provide any personally identifiable information to use our services. We don't ask for personal information.   
We may collect and use the following kinds of personal data: information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website, such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, operating system, referral source, length of visit, number of visitors and number of page views.   
We never collect personally identifiable information about users such as names, e-mail addresses or telephone numbers.   
Non-personally identifiable information such as IP address or browser type will be collected.   
We collect statistics using Google Analytics, and these statistics include: number of users, page views, countries, languages, browsers, keywords searched. We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of this website. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html .   
This website does not deliver pop-up or spyware or viruses of any kind.   
**Cookies and web beacons**   
This website or the advertisers on the website may use cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process.   
A cookie is a small text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.   
A web beacon (also called a clear gif or pixel tag) is a 1x1 pixel .gif image that advertisers place on their webpages. When you visit these pages, the web beacons can send your browser type, IP address, and other basic information to a server so advertisers can analyze the effectiveness of their ad campaigns. If you'd like to opt-out of web beacon tracking, you can clear your cookies.   
However these cookies are not used to extract any information from you. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies. We do not track or monitor these "cookies".   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   
Our advertisers may send you cookies to collect data in the advertising serving process. Any information collected from users by advertisers using cookies within this website is not subject to this website privacy policy, but rather the privacy policy of the individual advertiser.   
**Policy amendments**   
We may update this privacy policy from time to time by posting a new version on our website.   
You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.   
**Third party websites**   
The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this website only. This website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of third party websites. If you link to other websites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
